So, I have a question for you.
What's your score if you get down to no cards left on the board?
I think I have the answer.
We've gotten down pretty far.
We've got just several cards left on our board, and we've, we know we're going to get a pretty decent score.
I've got two cards left to play.
There's an eight, no help.
And then a four.
You'll note, all these cards are in sequence, so I just need to make sure I play them in the right order to win the hand.
First thing I'm going to do is I'm going to pull this three off, and this four over here.
And then I'll play this five, four, five, six, seven, six.
I've cleared the board.
I've got no cards left in my down cards.
What's my score?
Zero.
I know you can't get that in a real game of golf, but you can in golf solitaire.
Congratulations on a great score on this hand.